Guide to the Chaplain's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Chaplain's Office, Yale University, records
1939-2007
RU 1045
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
39.25
(41 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, memoranda, minutes, prayers, sermons, newsletters, bulletins, and subject files documenting the Yale Chaplain's Office and religious activities at Yale.
Yale University. Chaplain's Office
Biographical / Historical
The office of University Chaplain was established in 1927. The mission of the Chaplain's Office is to foster an understanding of and appreciation for the diverse religious and spiritual life of the Yale University community. It sponsors programs that encourage learning about the various religious traditions and spiritual practices of members of the University community, collaborates with the Yale Religious Ministry, and works with students, faculty and staff. The Chaplain's Office also provides services such as counseling, student program support, and pastoral care. It supports the University's interest in the city of New Haven through its liaison work with the community and through support of the Church of Christ in Yale. The following have served as University Chaplains: Rev. Elmore McKee (1927-1932); Rev. Sidney Lovett (1932-1958); Rev. William Sloane Coffin, Jr. (1958-1976); Rev. John Vannorsdall (1976-1985); Rev. Harry B. Adams (1986-1992); Rev. Frederick J. Streets (1992-2007); and Sharon Kugler (2007- ).
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 39-A (YRG 39-A), Records documenting official religious activities at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Chaplain's Office, 2007-2012.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, memoranda, minutes, prayers, sermons, newsletters, bulletins, and subject files documenting the Yale Chaplain's Office and religious activities at Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Church work; College students -- Religious life; Universities and colleges -- Religion; Yale University -- Religion; Yale University -- Religious life; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Chaplain's Office; Yale College (1718-1887). Church of Christ
- Chaplain's Office records, 1939-1989; Accession 2007-A-182
  Conditions Governing Access
  Materials in boxes 1- 14 are restricted until Jan 1, 2024 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.; materials in boxes 15-16 are open for research.
  - Administrative Records
    - 1973-1976
      - Coffin Dinner, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Church School, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Council, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Deacons, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Battell Engagement Calendar, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Battell and Hunger, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6 - 7)
      - CCA, DCM, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - EVC Returns, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Flower Memorials, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Freshmen Conference, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - YRM, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - YDS, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Yale Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Weekly Calendar/Releases, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - UMHE, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - V correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Campus Ministry, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Personnel, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Preachers, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Rockefeller, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Cafe information, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1976-1977
      - Misc. Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Church Council Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 24 - 25)
      - UCC School, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - UCC Finances, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27 - 28)
      - Food Drive, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Monthly Financial Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Preaching engagements, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Summer Term Schedule, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - The Presbytery, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Preachers, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Phil Zaeder, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Plans for Renovation in Dwight-Chaplain's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Student Deacons, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Bills, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Battell Renovations, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Battell Financial Statement, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - UCC Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Press Releases, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 1977-1979
      - Minutes of the Church Council, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Newsletters/letters to congregation, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - UCC financial correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - UCC Intern Info, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - UCC General Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Summer Schedule, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Budget Expense Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 50 - 51)
      - Chaplain - Interoffice Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - UCC Church Council Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 53 - 54)
      - Rockefeller Fund for Theological Education, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Church School, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Freshmen Conference, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - UCC Financial Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Battell Schedule, Fall 1977 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Yale Religious Ministries Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - John Vannorsdall Sermons and Prayers, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 61 - 63)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - News, YDN, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Check register, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Newsletters, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Magazine Articles, Donna schaper, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Deacons, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Interoffice Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - Bills, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - Treasurer's Office, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - UCC Constitution, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Strike, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - Requisitions, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - Sacred Music, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Downtown Cooperative Ministries, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 78)
      - Dwight Hall, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Freshperson Conference, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - Preacher's Schedule and Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Preaching Engagements, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 83)
      - Personnel, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - Dining hall bills, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - Vietnam Memorial Dedication Correspondence, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - 1978-1989
      - Annual Report, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Office Administration, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Associate Chaplaincy, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 89)
      - YRM, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 90)
      - Henri Nouwen, Battell Forum "Soundings", 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 91)
      - Church, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 92)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 93 - 94)
      - Miscellaneous, 1964-1980 (Box 4, Folder 95 - 96)
      - Protestant Hour Sermons, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 97)
      - Summer, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 99 - 100)
      - Recommendations, circa 1982 (Box 4, Folder 101)
      - Politics, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - Tax Reform, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - Unification Church, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Energy, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Peace, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 106 - 108)
      - Draft/Military, circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - 1979-1981
      - Preachers and Services, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 110)
      - Preaching engagements, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 111)
      - Opening Days, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 112)
      - Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 113)
      - Lent, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 114)
      - Lasker Sculpture, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 115)
      - Interns, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 116 - 117)
      - Fund for Theological Education, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 118 - 119)
      - Freshmen Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 120)
      - Council, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 121 - 122)
      - Church, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 123)
      - Choir, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 124)
      - CCY Charges, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 125)
      - Bills, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 126)
      - Battell Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 127)
      - Associate Search, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 128 - 129)
      - Acting Assistant Chaplain, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 130)
      - Associate Chaplaincy, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 131)
      - Report Forms, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 132)
      - Annual Report, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 133)
      - Choir Director, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 134)
      - CCY Fiscal Year, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 135)
      - Council, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 136)
      - Opening Days, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - 1981-1982
      - Yale Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 138)
      - Service of Remembrance, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 139)
      - Laurie Ruttenberg, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 140)
      - Protestant Hour, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - Preaching Engagements, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 142)
      - Billy Graham, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 143)
      - Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 144)
      - YRM, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 145)
      - Weekly Calendar/Releases, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 146)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 147 - 150)
      - Interns, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 151)
      - Freshmen Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 152)
      - Draft, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 153)
      - CCY Benevolence Applications, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 154)
      - Mabel Brooks, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 155)
      - Chipped China, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 156)
      - Wednesday Communion, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 157)
      - Birthday Party, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 158)
      - Church, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 159)
      - Church School, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 160)
      - Church Council, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 161)
      - Dimly Burning Wicks, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 162)
      - UCC Desk Calendar and Plan Book, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - 1982-1983
      - Yale Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 164)
      - Summer Letters, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 165)
      - Social Action, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 166 - 167)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 168 - 170)
      - Service of Remembrance, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 171)
      - Preachers and Services, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 172)
      - Protestant Hour, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 173)
      - Battell Schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 174)
      - Branford Calendar, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 175)
      - Preaching Engagements, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 176)
      - Opening Days, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 177)
      - Newsletters, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 178)
      - Ivy League Chaplains, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 179)
      - Church School, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 180)
      - Interns, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 181)
      - Draft, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 182)
      - Council, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 183)
      - Church, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 184)
      - CarEth/Peace, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 185)
      - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 186)
      - Freshman Conference, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 187)
      - Advice and Counsel Brunch, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 188)
      - YRM, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 189)
      - Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 190)
    - 1983-1984
      - Preaching Engagements, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 191)
      - Protestant Hour, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 192)
      - Review Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 193)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 194)
      - Preachers and Services, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 195)
      - Newsletters, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 196)
      - Opening Days, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 197)
      - Articles and Lectures, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 198)
      - Church, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 199)
      - Church School, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 200)
      - Credo, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 201)
      - Freshmen Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 202)
      - Fund for Theological Education, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 203)
      - Interns, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 204)
      - Intern Applications, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 205)
      - Letters of Welcome, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 206)
      - Service of Remembrance, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 207)
      - Short Women's Action, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 208)
      - Yale Memos, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 209)
      - YRM, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 210)
      - Summer Mailing, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 211)
      - Summer, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 212)
      - Social Action, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 213)
      - Battell Desk Calendar, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 214)
    - 1984-1985
      - Battell Schedule, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 215)
      - Summer, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 216)
      - Treasurer's Office, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 217)
      - Interoffice Correspondence (Yale Memos), 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 218)
      - YRM, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 219)
      - Newsletters, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 220)
      - Freshmen Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 221)
      - Interns, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 222)
      - Letters of Welcome, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 223)
      - New Members, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 224)
      - Church School, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 225)
      - Church Council, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 226)
      - Draft, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 227)
      - UCC Records, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 228)
      - Articles and Lectures, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 229)
      - Preaching Engagements, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 230)
      - Prayer Booklet, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 231)
      - Preachers and Services, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 232)
      - Opening Days, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 233)
      - Protestant Hour, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 234)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 235)
      - Service of Remembrance, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 236)
      - Social Action, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 237)
    - 1985-1986
      - Ellen Logan/Battell Chapel Schedule, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 238)
      - Interoffice Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 239)
      - YRM, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 240)
      - Treasurer's Office, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 241)
      - Summer, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 242)
      - Social Action, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 243)
      - Service of Remembrance, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 244)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 245)
      - Preaching Engagements, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 246)
      - Letters of Welcome, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 247)
      - Preachers and Services, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 248)
      - Lenten Booklet, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 249)
      - Intern Reunion, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 250)
      - Interns, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 251)
      - Freshperson Conference, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 252)
      - Holy Week, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 253)
      - Draft, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 254)
      - UCC Council, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 255)
      - Church School Adult Education, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 256)
      - Church Records, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 257)
      - Associate Chaplain Applications, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 258)
    - 1986-1987
      - Interoffice Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 259)
      - Summer, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 260)
      - Preachers and Services, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 261)
      - Treasurer's Office, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 262 - 264)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 265)
      - Service of Remembrance, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 266)
      - Social Action, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 267)
      - Ad hoc Committee on Structure, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 268)
      - Opening Days, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 269)
      - Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 270)
      - Letters of Welcome, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 271)
      - Lenten Booklet, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 272)
      - Interns, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 273)
      - Holy Week, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 274)
      - Freshperson Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 275)
      - Deacons, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 276)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 277)
      - UCC Church, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 278)
      - UCC Council, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 279)
      - Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 280)
    - 1987-1988
      - Battell Use Calendar, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 282)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 283)
      - MLK Service, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 284)
      - Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 285)
      - Opening Days, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 286)
      - Newsletter "Happenstance", 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 287)
      - Preference Cards (Entrance Letters), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 288)
      - Freshperson Conference, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 289)
      - Dwight Hall Usage, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 290)
      - UCC Council, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 291)
      - Church, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 292)
      - Christmas Eve Service, '87, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 293)
      - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 294)
      - Bulletin Question, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 295)
      - ANC School Support Project, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 296)
      - Battell Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 297)
      - UCC Summer Worship Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 298 - 299)
      - Opening Days, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 300)
      - Service of Remembrance, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 301)
      - Social Action, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 302)
      - Sermons and Prayers, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 303)
      - Preachers and Services, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 304)
      - UCC Pledge Letter, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 305)
      - Operating Budget, Treasurer's Office, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 306 - 308)
      - Yale Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 309)
      - YRM, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 310)
      - Battell Schedule, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 311)
      - Holy Week, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 312)
      - Interns, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 313)
      - Jefferson Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 314)
      - Lenten Booklet, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 315)
  - Social Issues
    - Draft Information, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 316 - 322)
    - Hardship Fund, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 323 - 327)
    - Hardship Fund -paid A-M, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 328 - 329)
    - Hardship Fund -paid N-Z, circa 1980 (Box 14, Folder 330 - 331)
    - Hardship Fund -pending, circa 1980 (Box 14, Folder 332)
    - Peace Week, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 333)
    - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 334)
  - Certificate for release of Walter Wagoner to serve as armed forces chaplain, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 335)
  - Programs for University events, 1942-1954, 1979, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 336)
  - Battell Worship Bulletins
    - 1939-1954 (Box 15, Folder 337 - 348)
    - 1965-1973 (Box 15, Folder 349 - 366)
    - 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 367 - 389)
    - 1983 Dec-1985 (Box 16, Folder 390 - 395)
    - Undated (Box 16, Folder 396)
- Chaplain's Office records, 1985-2005; Accession 2007-A-220
  Unpublished records are restricted until January 1, 2040; bulletins and newsletters are available for research.
  - Administrative Records
    These records are restricted until January 1, 2040.
    - 1989-1990
      - Preachers and Services, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Opening Days and Univ. Directory Listing, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Resolutions, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Meditation (Sacred and Profane), 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Social Action, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Worship and Prayers Summer, circa 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Happenstance, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Dwight Hall, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Lent, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Interns, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Fresh Person Conference, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1990-1991
      - Preachers and Services, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Social Action, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Services and Remembrance, circa 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Summer, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Lenten Booklet, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - War and Prayers for Peace, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Holy Week, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Interns, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Opening Days, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Happenstance, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Fund for Theological Education, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Fresh Person Conference, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Welcome Letters to Grad. Students (Entering Letters), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Dwight Hall, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Council, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Church School Adult Education, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - CCY report, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Yale Memos, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1991-94
      - Hymnal Project, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Fighting Back (Social Action), 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 31 - 32)
      - Opening Days, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Church School Adult Education, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Council, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Dwight Hall, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Entering Letters, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Fresh Person Conference, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Church School Adult Education, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Council, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Entering Letters, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Fresh Person Conference, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - CCY report, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Yale Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Summer, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Preachers and Services, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Services and Remembrance, circa 1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Social Action, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Ellington Vespers, circa 1994 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Countryman - Background Poetry, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Fresh Person Conference, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Lenten Booklet, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Countryman - Publicity etc, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - Holy Week, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Yale Religious Ministry (YRM) Notes
    - Notes and Minutes
      - 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 57 - 59)
    - Covenant, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Notes and Minutes
      - 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 61 - 62)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 63 - 64)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 65 - 66)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 67 - 68)
    - Religious Guidelines, Circa 1987-88 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Minutes and Notes
      - 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 70 - 71)
      - 1994 (Yale copy) (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 73 - 74)
    - Agenda, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Cynthia's Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Minutes and Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Membership Subcommittee, circa 1995 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Covenants and Attendance, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Covenant, circa 1994 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Minutes, Agenda, Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 81 - 82)